freeshipping.org 2009-12-07

# Privacy Policy for FreeShipping.org

Our Privacy Policy was developed in order to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us, and to ensure you that all information you provide will be kept in confidence and treated with respect. After reading this guide you should be capable of making informed decisions when using our site. 

**What Type of Information Do We Collect?**  
There is two types of information that you may provide to us while you are visiting our website "Active Information" and "Passive Information" 

Active information includes any personal information you actively choose to disclose. This may include your email address or any comments you submit to the site. At no time will your email address be made public. We use Active Information for administration purposes, to provide customer service and support. We may use the Active Information you provide to us to contact you about changes to our site, new free shipping coupons and deals, new services, features or products we offer, or other information we think you shall find valuable. If at any time you do not wish to receive such information, please send us an email at [contact@freeshipping.org](mailto:contact@freeshipping.org?subject=Privacy%20Policy). 

Passive information is collected in a way not visible to you, on an aggregate anonymous basis as you and others browse our site. We use a common internet technology called "cookies" to provide us with information about how our site is used. The information gathered may include the site pages viewed, the date and time of visits, time spent at our site, as well as the web sites visited just prior to or just after your visit our site. Passive Information is collected anonymously. If you do not wish to transmit "cookie" information about yourself, you may turn off the cookie function in your web browser. 

**What is an HTTP Cookie?**  
HTTP Cookies are parcels of text sent by a server to a web browser and then sent back unchanged by the browser each time it accesses that server. Cookies are used for authenticating, tracking, and maintaining specific information about users. Cookies allows web servers to recognize the computer used to access a site and simplify subsequent interactions with that site by the same user or to use the information to streamline the user's transaction on related web pages. Cookies makes it easier for a user to move from web site to web site and to complete transactions over the Internet. Cookies can make your online experience easier and more personalized. 

**How We Use the Information We Collect?**  
We use Passive Information to gather information about our users and to enhance the functionality and design our web site to make it easier to navigate. The Cookies we collect provide us with statistics about how many people visit our site, when they visit, as well as how they use our service. We do not connect any of this information to your personal information or email address. 

We secure your personal information by using reasonable efforts to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, or accidental loss or destruction of either active or passive information. Communications you may have with us via email or U.S. Mail may not be 100% secure therefore, if you choose to communicate with us through these means, you are assuming the risk of doing so and we request that you do not send or post sensitive information through these means.   
fr  
**Linking To Other Sites**  
You are be able to access other websites through FreeShipping.org. When you do so you are doing so subject to their policies regarding privacy and data collection and you should read those sites' privacy policies to make sure you agree to them before using such sites. When you choose to shop at such sites, you should read their privacy policies to make sure you agree to them before making purchases. 

**Sharing Information with Advertisers or Other Third Parties**  
We may disclose anonymous information about user habits, characteristics and user patterns, based on aggregate user statistics to advertisers on our site. No personal or active information will be shared with third parties. 

**Sharing Information with the Government or As Otherwise Required by Law**  
We may be required by law or government agency to disclose both Active and Passive Information you have provided to us. 

**No Use of Our Site by Persons Under 13**  
No person under 13 should disclose information on this site. You may learn more about protecting children's privacy online by visiting www.ftc.gov/kidzprivacy. 

**How Can You Choose Not to Receive Information By Us or to Correct, Delete or Access Your Information**  
If you desire not to receive information from us via email or if you wish to access, delete or correct your information, please send us an email to [contact@freeshipping.org](mailto:contact@freeshipping.org?subject=Privacy%20Policy). 

_We reserve the right to revise this policy at our discretion. Please check back on this site as this policy may be revised from time to time without notice to you._

_This Policy was last updated December 2nd 2007._
